moblized.com 2018-10-07

# Privacy Policy - Moblized

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Moblized.com and Moblized and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Moblized include Moblized.com. The Moblized website is a commerce application marketplace site. By using the Moblized website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

Moblized may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Moblized's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. Moblized may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age and gender. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Moblized. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Moblized website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Moblized's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Moblized encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Moblized so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Moblized is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Moblized website.

Use of your Personal Information

Moblized collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Moblized may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Moblized and its affiliates. Moblized may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Moblized does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Moblized may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is transferred to the third party. Moblized may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Moblized, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Moblized may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Moblized, in order to determine what Moblized services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Moblized to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Moblized will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Moblized or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Moblized; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Moblized, or the public.

Use of Cookies

The Moblized website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Moblized pages, or register with Moblized site or services, a cookie helps Moblized to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Moblized website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Moblized features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Moblized services or websites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

Moblized secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

Children Under Thirteen

Moblized does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

Disconnecting your Moblized Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your Moblized account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR MOBLIZED ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may learn how to disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting their "My Account" page. Users may also contact us via email or telephone..

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Moblized by contacting us here:

\- Email: [opt-out@moblized.com](mailto:opt-out@moblized.com)

\- Phone: 800-715-1327

Changes to this Statement

Moblized will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Moblized encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Moblized is protecting your information.

Contact Information

Moblized welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Moblized has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Moblized at:

Moblized

929 E. Center St.

Warsaw, Indiana 46580

Email Address:

Telephone number:

800-715-1327

Effective as of November 13, 2013
